Guide to the Graphics collection, 1740-1995 MS2379
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Graphics, 1740-1995; Series 1
  - Observatory Georgetown College (dry plate) by T.R.P., Circa [19--?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 24 x 19 cm. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Georgetown University Pictorial works.; Georgetown University. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00533520; Astronomical observatories Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Astronomical observatories. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00819649; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Movie stars' war bond sales campaign, Aug. 31, 1942., Circa [1942?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 343
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; War bond rally in Washington, D.C.
  - Harvey's Famous Restaurant, 11th and Pennsylvania Ave., Washington, D.C.., Circa [192-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 344
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Harvey's Restaurant, established 1858.
    Harvey's Restaurant (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Harvey's Famous Restaurant, 1107 Connecticut Ave., N.W., Washington, D.C., established 1858 by Underwood and Underwood Studios., Circa [193-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 345
  - [Harvey's Restaurant]., Circa 192-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 14 x 9 cm. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 346
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Title devised by cataloger.; Harvey's Restaurant, established 1858; shown at the 11th and Pennsylvania Ave., Washington, D.C. address.
  - Pennsylvania Avenue at night showing searchlight from the Raleigh on the Washington Monument., Circa 192-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 10 x 15 cm. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 347
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Raleigh Hotel, at Pennsylvania Ave. and 12th St., N.W., Washington, D.C.
    Raleigh Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Raleigh Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01790810; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The Ebbitt House, Washington, D.C.: headquarters Army and Navy, C.C. Willard, prop'r by Phoenix Lith. Company., Circa [18--?]; Series 1; 1 print: planographic, color; image 7 x 11 cm. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 348
    Cataloging notes: On verso is list: "Principal places of interest in Washington."; Ebbitt House, a hotel at 14th and F Streets, N.W., Washington, D.C.; existed from the 1860's until closed in 1925.
    Ebbitt House (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Ebbitt House (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00773721; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Ebbitt House., Circa 18--?]; Series 1; 1 print: planographic; image 8 x 7 cm. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 349
    Cataloging notes: On verso is a paragraph describing two portraits in the hotel: Two old portraits.; Ebbit House, a hotel at 14th and F Streets, N.W., Washington, D.C.; existed from the 1860's until closed in 1925.
  - Arlington-Ho??tel by H. Barban., Circa 1882?]; Series 1; 1 print: planographic; image 12 x 8 cm. (Box 14, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 350
    Cataloging notes: Publication date from pencil notation on printing.; Arlington Hotel, on Vermont Ave. at 15th and K St., N.W. in Washington, D.C.; now demolished.
  - Statler Hotel after fire Feb. 8, construction work Feb. 21, 1942., Circa [1942]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 351
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Statler Hotel in Washington, D.C., at 16th and K Streets, N.W.; shown under construction, after Feb. 8, 1942 fire.
    Statler Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Statler Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00775777; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Statler Hotel, D.C., from L Street, Aug. 1941., Circa [1941]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 8 x 12 cm. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 352
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Statler Hotel in Washington, D.C., at 16th and K Streets, N.W.; shown under construction.
  - Statler Hotel, D.C., from K Street, Aug. 1941., Circa [1941]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 8 x 11 cm. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 353
  - George Washington Hotel, 15th and New York Ave photograph by Leet Brothers., Circa [190-?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 354
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; George Washington Hotel in Washington, D.C. at 15th and New York Avenue, N.W. Replaced by the Washington Building.
    Washington Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00725008; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Shoreham Hotel, 15th and H Streets photograph by Leet Brothers., Circa [192-?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 21 x 25 cm. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 355
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Shoreham Hotel at 15th and H Streets, N.W., Washington, D.C.: hotel now at 2500 Calvert Street, N.W.
    Shoreham Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Shoreham Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01792539; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Union Hotel., Circa [187-?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 13 x 19 cm. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 356
    Cataloging notes: Copy of picture presented to the Oldest Inhabitants Association of the District of Columbia, by Alice D. Goddard and Frederick J. Goddard, In memory of their father, the late James Goddard. DGW; Union Hotel in Washington, D.C., 30th and M Streets, N.W.; built in 1795.
    Union Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Willard property north side Pennsylvania Avenue between 14th and 15th., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 13 x 19 cm. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 357
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Property belonging to Willard Hotel in Washington, D.C.; shows row of buildings.
    Willard Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Willard Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00663413; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The White House, view in Washington photograph by Leet Brothers., Circa [19--?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 21 x 25 cm. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 358
    Cataloging notes: Photoprint of 19th century printing.; Willard's City Hotel, in Washington, D.C. at 14th and Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W., with White House in background.
    White House (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Willard Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; White House (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631324; Willard Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00663413; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Willard Hotel photograph by Leet Brothers., Circa [18--?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 359
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Willard Hotel, in Washington, D.C. at 14th and Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W.
  - Old Willard Hotel, 14th and Pennsylvania Avenue photograph by Leet Brothers., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 360
  - Harvey's Famous Restaurant, 1107 Connecticut Ave., N.W., Washington, D.C--established 1858., Circa [193-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 361
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Harvey's Restaurant, established 1858. Differs from similar postcard with same title in presence of color and different arrangement of cars on the street.
  - Washington House, cor. 3d Street and Penn. Ave., Washington, D.C.., Circa 187-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 362
    Washington House (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Olmsted's, 1336 G Street, N.W. graficolour made by Grafico., Incorporated., Circa [195-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 363
    Olmsted's Restaurant (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Fort Washington., Circa 1874?]; Series 1; 1 print: planographic; image 11 x 15 cm. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Washington: U.S. Navy Yard lith. by E. Sachse and Company., Circa [186-?]; Series 1; 1 print: planographic, color; image 11 x 13 cm. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 365
    Cataloging notes: Washington Navy Yard, established 1799.
  - U.S. Navy Yard., Circa 186-?]; Series 1; 1 print: intaglio, hand color; sheet 7 x 11 cm. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 366
    Cataloging notes: Sheet trimmed to or within plate mark.; Washington Navy Yard, established 1799.
  - The Union Army disbanded by J.E. Taylor., Circa 1881?]; Series 1; 1 print: planographic; image 12 x 19 cm. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 367
    Cataloging notes: Publication date from pencil notation on printing.; Union Army marching in Washington at end of the Civil War, with the Capitol building in the background.
    United States. Army History Civil War, 1861-1865 Pictorial works.; United States. Army. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00533532; American Civil War (1861-1865) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01351658; 1861 - 1865 fast; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - George Percy Barse, Chief Judge of Municipal Court of the District of Columbia by Chase Limited, Photo., Circa 1954; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 19 x 13 cm. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 368
    Cataloging notes: Title from label on verso of photoprint.; Judge Barse, alumnus of George Washington University, A.B. 1917.
    Barse, George Percy Portraits.; Judges Washington (D.C.) Portraits.; George Washington University Alumni and alumnae Portraits.
  - Infantry encampment: Paterson's camp, Calorama, near Georgetown D.C., Washington, June 1, 1861 drawn by Kollner., Circa [June 1, 1861]; Series 1; 1 drawing; image 17 x 30 cm. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 369
    Cataloging notes: Civil War encampment in Kalorama, Washington, D.C.
    American Civil War (1861-1865) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01351658; 1861 - 1865 fast; Washington (D.C.) History Civil War, 1861-1865 Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Fort near Washington., Circa [19--?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 18 x 24 cm. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 370
    Cataloging notes: Original: U.S. Signal Corps photo B-383 (Brady Collection), National Archives, Washington, D.C.; Photographer from: Forts DeRussy, Stevens, and Totten / by Lenard E. Brown.; Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Civil War fort near Washington, showing a magazine and several seacoast carriages.
    American Civil War (1861-1865) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01351658; 1861 - 1865 fast; Fortification Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Fortification. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00933024; Washington (D.C.) History Civil War, 1861-1865 Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Fort Carroll Barracks, near Geisboro Point., Circa [19--?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 19 x 26 cm. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 371
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Original: National Archives, Washington, D.C.; Fort Carroll, a Civil War fort on the eastern side of the Potomac River in Washington, D.C.; its guns could sweep the Potomac north to the Washington Arsenal and the Navy Yard.
    Fort Carroll (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Fortification Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) History Civil War, 1861-1865 Pictorial works.
  - Fort Greble., Circa [19--?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 18 x 24 cm. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 372
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Original: National Archives, Washington, D.C.; Interior of Fort Greble, a Civil War fort on the eastern side of the Potomac River in Washington, D.C., opposite Alexandria, Va.; shows open magazines, gun emplacements and ammunution stacked nearby.
    Fort Greble (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Fortification Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) History Civil War, 1861-1865 Pictorial works.
  - Navy Yard, showing the 7th New York Volunteer Infantry., Circa [19--?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 19 x 26 cm. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 373
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Original: probably in the National Archives, Washington, D.C.; Washington Navy Yard, Civil War era.
    Washington Navy Yard Pictorial works.; United States. Army. Regiment Infantry, New York Volunteers, 7th (1861-1863) Pictorial works.
  - Fort Totten, near Soldiers' Home., Circa [19--?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 18 x 24 cm. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 374
    Cataloging notes: Original: U.S. Signal Corps photo B-376 (Brady Collection), National Archives.; Photographer from: Forts DeRussy, Stevens, and Totten / by Lenard E. Brown.; Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Interior of Fort Totten, Civil War fort in northern part of Washington, D.C.
    American Civil War (1861-1865) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01351658; 1861 - 1865 fast; Fortification Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Fortification. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00933024; Fort Totten (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) History Civil War, 1861-1865 Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Washington (D.C.) Fort Totten. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01325053; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Mellon Art Gallery, view from southwest., Circa [1939?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 15, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 375
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; National Gallery of Art under construction; established 1937 through gift of Andrew W. Mellon, to the United States, of a collection of paintings and of a fund for its housing; opened 1941.
    National Gallery of Art (U.S.) Pictorial works.; National Gallery of Art (U.S.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00532733; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Mellon Art Gallery looking north on 6th St., Dec. 26, 1939., Circa [1939]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 376
  - Jefferson Memorial, Nov. 1939., Circa [1939]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 377
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Thomas Jefferson Memorial in Washington, D.C.; completed in 1942; shows Memorial under construction.
    Thomas Jefferson Memorial (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Thomas Jefferson Memorial (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01150173; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Jefferson Memorial from a distance, Nov. 1939., Circa [1939]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 378
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Thomas Jefferson Memorial in Washington, D.C.; completed in 1942; shows a distance view of the Memorial under construction.
  - Jefferson Memorial, April 11, 1942., Circa [1942]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 379
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Thomas Jefferson Memorial in Washington, D.C., completed in 1942; shows finished Memorial.
  - Lincoln Memorial., Circa [1942?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 6 x 9 cm. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 380
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Memorial to Abraham Lincoln in Washington, D.C.; dedicated 1922; view from a distance.
    Lincoln Memorial (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Lincoln Memorial (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00999000; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Lincoln Memorial interior., Circa [1942?]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 14 x 8 cm. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 381
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Interior of Lincoln Memorial showing statue of Abraham Lincoln; Memorial in Washington, D.C.; dedicated 1922.
  - Southwest from south side of the Lincoln Memorial, June 7, 1942., Circa [1942]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 382
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; View from Lincoln Memorial in Washington, D.C.; dedicated 1922.
  - From Lincoln Memorial, June 7, 1942., Circa [1942]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 383
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; View of Potomac River from Lincoln Memorial, Washington, D.C.
    Lincoln Memorial (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Lincoln Memorial (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00999000; Potomac River Pictorial works.; United States Potomac River. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01245982; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Toward Lincoln Memorial from 17th Street, June 7, 1942., Circa [1942]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 384
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; View from a distance of the Lincoln Memorial in Washington, D.C.; dedicated in 1922.
  - Southwest from west side of Lincoln Memorial, June 7, 1942., Circa [1942]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 385
  - Site of Department of Commerce., Circa [between 1928 and 1930]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 8 x 14 cm (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 386
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Construction site of the Department of Commerce Building in Washington, D.C.; building on 15th between Constitution Ave. and D St., N.W.; building completed in 1932; Washington Monument in background.
    United States. Department of Commerce Pictorial works.; United States. Department of Commerce. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01852419; Washington Monument (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington Monument (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01170927; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Ericsson and Lincoln Memorials, Potomac Park., Circa [ 1930]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 7 x 9 cm. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 387
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; John Ericsson Memorial in Potomac Park, Washington, D.C.; Lincoln Memorial in background.
    John Ericsson Memorial (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Lincoln Memorial (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Grant statue at Capitol, 1928., Circa [1928]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 15 cm. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 388
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Ulysses S. Grant Memorial statue at the Capitol end of the Mall in Washington, D.C.; dedicated in 1922.
    Grant Memorial (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Bonus marchers, 1932., Circa [1932]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 389
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Encampment of Bonus marchers, unemployed veterans of military service, who demanded immediate payment of bonus voted them by Congress; they converged on Washington, D.C. between May and July, 1932.
    Bonus Expeditionary Force, 1932 Pictorial works.
  - Tents of Bonus marchers, 1932., Circa [1932]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 13 cm. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 390
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Tents at encampment of Bonus marchers, unemployed veterans of military service, who demand immediate payment of bonus voted them by Congress; they converged on Washington, D.C. between May and July, 1932.
  - Encampment of Bonus marchers, 1932., Circa [1932]; Series 1; 1 photoprint: black and white; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 391
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photoprint.; Encampment of Bonus Marchers, unemployed veterans of military service, who demanded immediate payment of bonus voted them by Congress; they converged on Washington, D.C. between May and July, 1932.
  - Statuary at Washington: Columbus, Liberty, Rescue., Circa 18--?]; Series 1; 1 print: planographic, color; image 12 x 19 cm. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 392
    Cataloging notes: Three statues in Washington, D.C.
    Statues Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Statues. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01132151; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Washington: statue of Washington lith. by E. Sachse and Company., Circa [186-?]; Series 1; 1 print: planographic, color; image 18 x 12 cm. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 393
    Cataloging notes: Horatio Greenough statue of Washington, as it stood on the United States Capitol grounds; now at the National Museum of American Art, a part of the Smithsonian Institution in Washington, D.C.
    Washington, George, 1732-1799 Statues Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington, George, 1732-1799. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00178100; Statues. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01132151; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874